Ing. Roman Ožana / Resume

Hi there,

my name is Roman Ožana. I am a freelance webdesigner and developer with more than 14 years of experiences. I'm here to create websites and applications easy to use, intuitive and modern inside. I love tech startups and community around. Enjoy working in small and effective team.

Address: Prague, Přímětická st.

Web: https://ozana.cz
Email: roman@ozana.cz

Phone: +420 605 783 455



Work experiences

Co-founder and full stack developer at Testomato s.r.o.

March 2012 - present

Work as full time Javascript and PHP lead developer.

Full stack developer at Devel.cz Lab s.r.o.

October 2009 – present

Work as experienced PHP and Javascript developer mostly on zdrojak.cz.

Freelance web developer

October 2009 - present

Full stack developer and freelance web developer

14 years 7 months 23 days

11 years 6 months 22 days

12 years 4 months 23 days

Application Engineer at Intergraph s.r.o.

July 2010 - April 2011

Application Engineer (external consultant) – testing of corporate solution for metadata sharing and managing. Developing of simple C# .NET applications.

PHP developer at Skvely.CZ s.r.o.

1 year 5 months

9 months

March 2009 - July 2010

Works there as web application developer mostly in PHP and developing some modules for e-commerce Magento.

Tech Stack

Server side Php PHP (S) NodeJS Client side Js Javascript F HTML5 Tailwind CSS B Bootstrap **3** CSS3 React **U**jQuery **Frameworks** N NextJS Angular JS **Z** Zend Framework mette Nette Framework **Databases** 🏹 MySQL MongoDB **Redis Code quality** AVA AVA PHP PhpUnit **Cy** Cypress Mocha **Bundlers** Makefile **Webpack** Parcel **DevStack macOS** A Linux Docker PhpStorm X Visual Studio Code **Git** Languages Czech - native language English - communicative Additional Info Driving license: B

Education

VŠB – Technical University of Ostrava

2002 - 2007: Geoinformatics

- Study program: Geodesy and cartography, Geoinformatics
- **Degree**: Master's degree (Msc., Geoingormatics)
- Address: VŠB Technical university of Ostrava, 17. listopadu 15, Ostrava Poruba, Faculty of Mining and Geology

SPŠE Rožnov pod Radhoštěm

1997 – 2001: Electronic computer systems

